Guide to the Student Action With Farmworkers Records, 1950-2013 and undated, bulk 1992-2010
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Student Projects Series, 1986-2011, and undated, (46 boxes)
  - Into the Fields: Documentary Work Subseries 1991-2010, and undated, (6 boxes)
    - Recollections of Home, 2000, (4 of 7) (Box 48)
      The Heart of Tradition, by: Anna Harvin
      Versos - Expressing Your Feelings, by: Benito Hernandez
      Knitting the Threads of Life - The Crocheted Works of Maria Baltazar, by: Monica Smith and Dulce Ibarra
      Food for Thought, by: Shana Jordan
      Retrato de Petra, by: Margarita Martinez; Title: Evolution of Culture through Farmwork
      Nirav Mehta; Title: A Dedication to the Migrant Farmworkers
      Rafhy Levi Bracero Figueroa
    - Recollections of Home, 2000, (5 of 7) (Box 48)
      Overcoming the Odds, by: Felipe Olvera
      Love in the Fields of NC, by: Leodoro Perales
      The Artesanía of Nicacio Reyes Reins, by: Jasmine Rocke and Laura Podolsky
      Federico and His Guitar, by: Raquel Rico
      Festival Foods, by: Terry Skorewics
    - Recollections of Home, 2000, (6 of 7) (Box 49)
      Title: Faith Meets Tradition - Baptism and Three-year old Presentation in One Migrant Family, by: Ana Viego
    - Recollections of Home, 2000, (7 of 7) (Box 49)
      Food for Thought, by: Shana Jordan, 2000 July 19
      Retrato de Petra, by: Margarita Martinez
      The Artesanía of Nicacio Reyes Reina, by: Laura Podolsky, 2000 July 30
      How Federico learned to play the guitar and some songs from his repertoire, by: Raquel Rico, 2000 July 21
      Festival Foods and Music, by: Terry Skorewicz, 2000 July 30
      Faith Meets Tradition, by: Ana Viego, 2000 August 11
    - Into the Fields 2001, (1 of 1) (Box 49)
      Interns' artwork.
    - 2001 Folklife Documentary Project, (1 of 5) (Box 49)
      Juan Flores' Favorite Pastime, by: Jean G. Mathurin, 2001 July 11
      Artesanía, by: Jean G. Mathuria, 2001 July 9
      Juan Flores' Belt making, by: Susan Hicks, 2001 July 9
      De Niña a Mujer, by: Erin Barker and Maria Ruelas
    - 2001 Folklife Documentary Project, (2 of 5) (Box 49)
      Words that Draw the Distance Near: The Poetry of a Migrant Farmworker and the Tradition of Family, by: Scott Pryor
      Carlos Mora's Hog Killing Tradition, by: Karla Rosenberg
      A Man's Promise to the Virgin Mary, by: Brian Eichner and Marivel Gomez
    - 2001 Folklife Documentary Project, (3 of 5) (Box 49)
      La Comida y La Familia, by: Enedelia Rios and Lundon B. Sims
      3rd Birthday Celebration, by: Sylvia Zapata
      Traditional Mexican Food/Meals, by: Curran Geist
      Youth Mural Project - We the future of two merging cultures, by: Curran Geist
    - 2001 Folklife Documentary Project, (4 of 5) (Box 49)
      Migrant Camp Food, by: Chris Watchson and Michael Sinohai, 2001 August
      La Banda y La Realidad, by: Beth O'Donnel and Hannah Armstrong, 2001 July
      Luis Miguel Tibocha, by: Ben Campos and Jesse Gonzalez, 2001 July
    - 2001 Folklife Documentary Project, (5 of 5) (Box 49)
      Religious Traditions on Hispanic Culture, by: Natasha McDonald, 2001 July
      One Generation to the Next: Stories in Hispanic Families, by: Lorena Alvarez, Laxmi Haynes, and Bill Norton, 2001 July
      Student Action with Farmworker's 2001 Into the Fields Program, by: n/a
    - Into the Fields Documentary Project Summer 2002, (1 of 2) (Box 49)
      Maribel Selgado, by: Gerardo Martinez, 2002 August
      Tea Time, by: Ann Plonk and Juana Ortiz, 2002 July
      Woodworker from Guanajuato, by: Andrea Waddle and Lorena Mendez, 2002 July
      Our Daily Bread, by: Alma Navarette and Raul de Anda, 2002 July
      Alacran's Apprentice, by: Nkechi Ukwu and Coby Jansen, 2002 July
      Art, Craft, and Design, by: Isabel Aguilar and Maggie Villagran, 2002 July
      Seira Reyes: An Artist's Journey, by: Samantha Fernandez and Lorena Magaña-Ortiz, 2002 August
    - Into the Fields Documentary Project Summer 2002, (2 of 2) (Box 49)
      Reactions on Labor Camps after the Theatre Group Performs, by: Daniel Mendez, 2001 August 4
      Fourth of July, by: Manuel Rodriguez and Hope Bastian, 2002 August 5
      Evening Mass in the Fields, by: Bonnie DeBlois, 2002 July
      Por Ser Mojado, by: Alicio Carvajal, 2002 July
      Home, Sweet Home, by: Lucina Benito and Elizabeth Smith, 2002 July
      Bertha Rendón, by: Hope Bastian, 2002 August
    - 2002 Folklife Documentary Project, (1 of 1) (Box 49)
      Genoveva Camacho's Traditional Practice of Making Herbal Medicinal Teas, by: Juana Z. Ortiz and Ann Plonk, July 2002
      Maribel Salgado, Folkloric Dancer; by: Gerardo Martinez, 2002 August 2
      Give us this day our daily bread, by: Alma Navarette and Raul de Anda, 2002 July
    - Into the Fields Folklife Documentary Project, Summer 2002, (1 of 4) (Box 49)
      Genoveva Camacho's Traditional Practice of Making Herbal Medicinal Teas, By: Juana Ortiz, 2002 July 26
      Maribel Salgado - Mexican Folkloric Dancer, by: Gerardo Martinez, 2002 Aug. 2
      Woodworking, by: Lorena Meridez
    - Into the Fields Folklife Documentary Project, Summer 2002, (2 of 4) (Box 49)
      'Give us this day our daily bread,' by: Alma Navarette and Raul de Anda
      Alacran's Apprentice, by: Coby Jansen and Nkechi Ukwu
      Art, Craft, and Design, by: Isabel Aguilar and Maggie Villagran
      Seira Reyes - An Artists Journey, by: Samantha Fernandez and Lorena Magaña-Ortiz
      Reactions on Labor Camps after the Theatre Group Performs, by: Daniel Mendez
    - Into the Fields Folklife Documentary Project, Summer 2002, (3 of 4) (Box 49)
      Evening Mass in the Fields, by: Bonnie DeBois
      Por Ser Mojado, by: Alicia Carvajal
      Home Sweet Home, by: Lucina Benito and Elizabeth Smith
    - Into the Fields Folklife Documentary Project, Summer 2002, (4 of 4) (Box 49)
      Bertha Rendon - Dueña del Restaurant Tacos Los Paisanos en Raeford, NC, by: Hope Bastian
      Slides from: Seira Reyes, Evening Mass in the Fields, 'Give us this day our daily bread,' Jose's Work, and Maribel Salgado
    - SAF spring convening, polaroid fun exercise, 2002, (1 of 1) (Box 49)
    - Harnett La 2002 summer program negatives, (1 of 1) (Box 49)
    - Into the Fields Documentary Projects 2003, (1 of 2) (Box 49)
      Children's Folklore - An Introduction to Mexican Kid's Songs, by: Maureen McNamerra and Emily Hall
      Crazy Taco - 'The Taste of Mexico' in Smithfield, NC, by: Kate Vyborny and Jose Morales
      Tropical Pica Flor, by: Seema Kakad
      Narcissa Santamaria Cubias, by: Alaina Burr
    - Into the Fields Documentary Projects 2003, (2 of 2) (Box 49)
      Here come the Padrones, by: Gina Humble
      Compartir Música con la Comunidad en el Nombre de Jesus Cristo, by: Rosie Sharples and Zoe Kelly
      Piñata Making, by: Claudia Ramos and Laura Johnson
      The Body and the Blood, by: Rachel Kuck and Gricel Gamino
      Manos Curativas, by: Dora Crus and Luis Gonzalez Jr.
      Jollas Artesanales, by: Nestor Barboza
    - Into the Fields Documentary Project 2003, (1 of 5) (Box 49)
      Children's Folklore: An Introduction to Mexican Kid's Songs, by: Maureen McNamara and Emily Hall
    - Into the Fields Documentary Project 2003, (2 of 5) (Box 49)
      Crazy Taco: 'The Taste of Mexico' in Smithfield, NC, by: Kate Vyborny and Jose Morales
    - Into the Fields Documentary Project 2003, (3 of 5) (Box 49)
      Mexican Customs for Newborns and Pregnant Women, by: Amanda Grove
      Manos Curativas, by: Dora Cruz and Luis Gonzalez Jr.
    - Into the Fields Documentary Project 2003, (4 of 5) (Box 50)
      Here Come the Padrones, by: Gina Humble
    - Into the Fields Documentary Project 2003, (5 of 5) (Box 50)
    - SAF Symposium Action at Publix, 2003, by Stephanie Etaine, (1 of 1) (Box 50)
    - SAF Symposium Action at Publix, 2003, by Stephanie Etaine slides, (1 of 1) (Box 50)
    - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride, Durham, NC, 2003 Sep. 30, by Laura Drey, (1 of 1) (Box 50)
    - Into the Fields Documentary Projects 2004, (1 of 4) (Box 50)
      De Punto a Puntado, by: Maria Negrete, 2004 July
      Mi Sufrimiento, by: Michael Hachey and Miguel A. Blancas
    - Into the Fields Documentary Projects 2004, (2 of 4) (Box 50)
      Healthy Cooking with Don Pablo, by: Elida Molina and Margaret Rife, 2004 July
      Pencil Drawing, By: Maria Cristina Gómez, 2004 June
      Music of Life, by: Alejandra Pérez and Remy Martinez, 2004 August
    - Into the Fields Documentary Projects 2004, (3 of 4) (Box 50)
      An Instrument of God, by: Natalie Lamela and Lyndsey Beutin, 2004 June
      Pedro Hernandez, by: Serene Myers and Joseph Lee, 2004 August
    - Into the Fields Documentary Projects 2004, (4 of 4) (Box 50)
      El Dia de la Cruz, by: Gabriela Rodriguez and Amanda Marshalls, 2004 July
      Passing the Time, Wire Scorpions and Volleyball in Henry Chancy Camp, by: Ann Warshaw and Carla Martinez
      Celebrations, by: Jessica Ramirez and Marya Millard, 2004 June-July
    - 2004 Celebrations, by: Jessica Ramirez and Manja Millard, (2 folders) (Box 50)
    - Into the Fields Folklife Documentary Projects, 2005, (1 of 3) (Box 50)
      Musical Talents by Fernando Camacho 'Musical Passion,' by: Guillermo Raya and Regnaldo Sosa
      Por la Vida que Nos a Brindado, by: Rocio Rangel and Noah Robert Raper
      Melchor Tomas - Life, Struggle, and Tradition of Latino Farmers, by: Morgan Gregson and Walter Ramirez
      Raíces Aztecas, by: Guadalupe Huitron, Jesus Escobar
    - Into the Fields Folklife Documentary Projects, 2005, (2 of 3) (Box 50)
      Untitled, by: Ana Gayton
      In the Kitchen with Mauro, by: Jaime Duggan
      Carrying the Taste of the Past into the Future, by: Joslyn Wiley and Alicia Marquez
      Passion for a Net, by: Jose de Jesus Franco and Maria Singleton
      Hablando y Alabando, by: Nakashia Dunner
    - Into the Fields Folklife Documentary Projects, 2005, (3 of 3) (Box 50)
      America Pavon - Cruzando la Frontera, by: Lupita Lopez and Julia Finkelstein
      Una Tradicíon que Cambia, by: Laura Bartels and Adelina Fuente
      El Guerro y la Hormiga, by: Ramon Zepeda and Nereida Arguijo
    - 2005 ITF Documentary Project by Carmela Meehan, (1 of 1) (Box 50)
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, (1 of 12) (Box 50)
      Working as a Family: Foundations of Educational Achievements and Aspirations, Farmworkers in North Carolina, by: Tom Allin and Kelley Haven, 2006 Dec. 14
      When the Leaves Begin to Fall, A Struggle for Education and the Better Life, by: Erik Anderson, Deon McCormick, 2006
      Mientras las Hojas Sigan Cayendo, by: Isabel G.N., 2004-2005
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, (2 of 12) (Box 50)
      Nada Mas, A Farmworker's Story of Family, Religion, and Work, by: Carina Barnett-Loro and Macey Stapleton, 2006, December 14
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, (3 of 12) (Box 50)
      Volunteering at the Proyecto de Trabajadores Agrícolas, by: Avery Resor, 2006
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, (4 of 12) (Box 50)
      I know how they're suffering in the fields, Leonardo Galvin's Journey from Farmworker to Advocate, by: Avery Resor and Paul Kliest, Jr., 2006 Dec. 14
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, (5 of 12) (Box 50)
      To Laugh and Cry at the Same Time, Veronica Alvarez-Coyt, by: Rebecca Fairchild, 2006 Dec. 14
      Working for Change, by: Youngjoo Ha and Glenn Love, 2006
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, (6 of 12) (Box 50)
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, (7 of 12) (Box 50)
      Dos Mundos, by: Miguel Perez; Title: Decisions Along the Way, by: Natashia Vasquez and Sarah Stephens
      Educational Aspirations, by: Jannah Tudiver
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, (8 of 12) (Box 50)
      Educational Aspirations, by: Jannah Tudiver (CDs contain sensitive material)
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, (9 of 12) (Box 50)
      Through the eyes of a tobacco worker, by: Luis Arreguin
      Rapture in the Fields, by: Erica Bondy, Aylwin Lo and Leonila Rivera
      Everyday Superman, by: Jessamyn Bowling and Amy Gellatly
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, (10 of 12) (Box 50)
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, (11 of 12) (Box 50)
      The Ever-Retreating Horizon of Equality, by: Dan Dwyer and Erica Bratz, 2006 August 8
    - SAF/CDs Our Stories/Our Dreams Documentary Project 2006, (12 of 12) (Box 50)
      Vida fuera del Campo, by: Jerrina Rodriguez and Jessica Calderon
      Ver por Adelante, by: Sanjuana Garcia and Mary Lohman
      Una Familia Guatemalteca, by: Benjamin Gaspar
    - CDS 2006 Intern Sara Scott (Archive Materials), (1 of 1) (Box 50)
    - 2006 Doc Intern Bart Evans, (1 of 1) (Box 50)
      Voices from the Fields, by: Bart Evans, 2006
      Release forms for Amelia Alexander, 2007 July
    - Documentary Projects, 2006-2007, (1 of 7) (Box 51)
      Through the eyes of a tobacco worker, by: Luis Arreguin, 2006
      Dos Mundos, by: Miguel Perez, 2006
      Educational Aspirations, by: Jessica Calderon and Jerrina Rodriguez, 2006
      Rapture in the Fields, by: Erica Bondy, Aylwin Lo and Leonila Rivera, 2006
      El Dúo Dinámico, by: Luisa Baeza and Yesica Orozco, 2007
      One of Many Success Stories, Juan Frias past and present, by: Heriberto Martinez, 2007
      Educational Aspirations, by: Deborah Cramer, 2007
    - Documentary Projects, 2006-2007, (2 of 7) (Box 51)
      Una mujer realizada, by: Kendal Walters, 2007
      Me toco mucho suerte... Eleuterio el Oportunista, by: Maria Banuelos and Alice Wheet, 2007
      Everyday Superman, by: Jessamyn Bowling and Amy Gellatly, 2006
      Ver por Adelante, by: SanJuana Garcia and Mary Lohman, 2006
    - Documentary Projects, 2006-2007, (3 of 7) (Box 51)
      A Taste of Mexico, by: Deborah Cramer, 2007
      Learning from Each Other, by: Liza Hayes-Lozado and Adriana Sanchez, 2007
      El trabajador de Tyson (The worker at Tyson), by: Jonathan Luna, 2007
    - Documentary Projects, 2006-2007, (4 of 7) (Box 51)
      The Pursuit of Success and Happiness, by: Meghan Antol and Oscar Vasquez, 2007
      Dos Vidas, Un Sueno (Two Lives, One Dream), by: Elizabeth Arias and Elizabeth Tomas, 2007
    - Documentary Projects, 2006-2007, (5 of 7) (Box 51)
      El Dúo Dinámico (The Dynamic Duo), by: Luisa Baeza and Yesica Orozco, 2007
      Me toco mucha suerte: Eleuterio el oportunista (I was touched by lots of luck: Eleuterio the opportunist), by: Maria Banuelos and Alice Wheet, 2007
    - Documentary Projects, 2006-2007, (6 of 7) (Box 51)
      Servidora de Dios (Servant of God), by: Maribel Maldonado and Charolette Sibley, 2007
      One of Many Success Stories: Juan Frias, by: Heriberto Martinez, 2007
    - Documentary Projects, 2006-2007, (7 of 7) (Box 51)
      Christmas Tree Family, by: Claire McLendon, 2007
      Una mujer realizada (A fully realized/complete woman), by: Kendal Walters, 2007
    - Summer 2007 Alix Blair Project Materials, (1 of 1) (Box 51)
    - 2007 Folklife Documentary Project, (1 of 2) (Box 51)
      Mystery Man Documentary, by: Maria Cristina Herrera, 2007 July
      Hidden Heroes of Farmworker Justice Movement, by: Jorja Cummings, 2007 July-August
      Rural and Migrant Ministry, by: Leah Russell, 2007 August 9
    - 2007 Folklife Documentary Project, (2 of 2) (Box 51)
      Title: The Sights of the Shore, by: Walker Somerville, 2007 August
    - 2008 Folklife Documentary Project, (1 of 1) (Box 51)
      Cristina, by: Rachel craft, Rachel McGill, and Pablo Buenrostro, 2008 Summer
      La Víbora en La Campana; by: Stephanie Gans, 2008 August
      Making Ripples, A Rope to Climb, by: Leanne Tory-Murphy, 2008 August
      Constructing a Future, Community Empowerment Through Education and Health, by: Pablo Buenrostro, Rachel Craft, Rachel McGill, 2008 Summer
      Educational Aspirations, by: Rebecca Crain, 2008 July
    - 2008 Documentary Project, (1 of 7) (Box 51)
      Quién Hablará por Ellos? Crónicas de un Trabajador Agrícola, by: Mariela Cedeño, 2008 January 8
      Mi vida es una prisión, mi corazón una canción, by: Amy Petrocy, 2008 August 8
      interview with Victor Mendoza, by: Amy Petrocy, 2008 June 29
    - 2008 Documentary Project, (2 of 7) (Box 51)
      Victor Mendoza's work (writings and drawings), by: Amy Petrocy, 2008 June 30
    - 2008 Documentary Project, (3 of 7) (Box 51)
      Don Juan Camacho, by: Jose David Lopez and George Lozano
    - 2008 Documentary Project, (4 of 7) (Box 51)
      Untitled, by: Leticia Perez, Reed Weatherill, and Tarynness (sic), 2008 August 8
    - 2008 Documentary Project, (5 of 7) (Box 51)
      The Giving Tree, by: Jackie Fitzgerald, 2008 August 6
      Patricio Bros - Unfinished Business, by: Jackie Fitzgerald, 2008 summer
    - 2008 Documentary Project, (6 of 7) (Box 51)
      Coincidental Encounter - Realistic meaning/cliché understanding, by: Yazmin Garcia Rico, 2008 August 3
    - 2008 Documentary Project, (7 of 7) (Box 51)
      Dreams Broken, Offers Rebuilt(?) - A Story of Juan Frias, by: Michael Ives Taylor, 2008 August 9
      Well, besides the pay, I like helping people, by: Barbie Spitz, 2008 August 8
      Farmworker's Wife, by: Hilario Chavez, Salvador Cordoso, 2008 August 9
    - SAF End of Summer Celebration, 2008, by Leanne Tory-Murphy (Box 51)
    - 2010 ITF, SSC and Theater Photos, (2 folders) (Box 51)
    - W-10: Yo también me puedo..., undated, (1 of 1) (Box 51)
      Picture book made by child
    - Photos from Dale Bones' farm by student, undated, (1 of 1) (Box 51)
    - Siera Reyes, (7 folders) (Box 51)
    - Miscellaneous protest photos, undated, (1 of 1) (Box 51)
    - Ni de Aquí, Ni de Allá (Not from Here/Not from There), Kreps Gallery at CDS (slides), undated, (1 of 1) (Box 51)
    - 110B (slides), undated, (1 of 1) (Box 51)
    - Unlabeled slides, artwork, undated, (1 of 1) (Box 51)
    - April's community organizing presentation at school, (1 of 1) (Box 51)
    - Pender Co AIM, undated, (1 of 1) (Box 51)
    - Staff scrapbooks 1-8, undated, (8 folders) (Box 51)
    - Miscellaneous media, undated, (1 of 1) (Box 51)
    - Miscellaneous subject photos, undated, (1-4 of 6 folders) (Box 51)
    - Miscellaneous subject photos, undated, (Folders 5-6) (Box 52)
    - Janeth (2nd book) negatives, (1 of 1) (Box 52)
    - Staff photo slides, (4 folders) (Box 52)
    - Unlabeled negatives, (5 folders) (Box 52)
    - 2 rolls of film, (1 of 1) (Box 52)
    - Title: The Heart of Tradition, by: Anna Harvin, 2000 Folklife Documentary Project (Box 53)
  - Into the Fields: Journals and Guided Reflections Subseries, 1995-2005
    Contains journals, notebooks, and worksheets kept by interns for the purpose of reflection on the internship and documentary process.
    - Journals and Guided Reflections, 1995-2001 (Box 54)
    - Journals and Guided Reflections, 2005-2009 (Box 55)
    - Journals and Guided Reflections, 2009, and undated (Box 56)
    - Faces of Mount Olive, By: Stephen Chin, 2000 (Box 94)
    - Title: Overcoming the Odds, By: Felipe Olvera Jr., 2000 Folklife Documentary Project (Box 94)
    - Title: Seira Reyes, An Artist's Journey, By: Samantha C. Fernandez and Lorena E. Magana-Ortiz, 2002 Student Action with Farmworkers (Box 94)
    - FLOC por la Justicia (Box 94)
    - PACE (Box 94)
  - AIM - Farmworker Class Subseries, 1993-2003, and undated, (3 boxes)
    Digital material moved to the Audio/Visual and Digital Material Subseries.
    - Administrative/general information, undated (Box 57)
    - Readings, 1993-2002 (Box 57)
    - Readings, undated (Box 57)
    - Projects, 2001-2002 (Box 57)
    - Project 2002: Mi Hogar (Box 58)
    - Projects, 2002 and undated (Box 59)
    - 2001 individual student files (Box 59)
    - Conferences and retreats 1998-2003 and undated (Box 59)
  - Levante Subseries, 1994-2011, and undated, (4 boxes)
    SAF's Levante Leadership Institute uses theatre and arts to provide migrant and farmworker youth in rural North Carolina with opportunities to build self-esteem, develop leadership skills, and prepare them for higher education. Series contains Levante administrative files as well as audio-visual documentation of theatre projects.
    A/V material moved to the Audio/Visual and Digital Material Subseries.
    - 1994-2001, (approximately 50 folders) (Box 60)
    - 2002-2011 and undated, (approximately 50 folders) (Box 61)
    - Cloth Banners, (4 banners) (Box 63)
  - Intern Referral Service Subseries, 1999-2000, (1 box)
    The Intern Referral Service links interested students with organizations in need of interns.
    - 1999-2006, (approximately 90 folders) (Box 64)
  - Audio/Visual and Digital Material Subseries, 1990-2004, and undated, (6 boxes)
    Contains audio, visual, and digital material from Into the Fields, AIM, and Levante interns' documentary projects.
    - (Box 62)
    - Theater release forms, transcripts, tape logs, 2004-2005, (7 folders) (Box 62)
    - Rough cut and back-up file CDs and DVDs (Box 62)
    - Levante: Theater for Social Change (rough cut) 15:55, VHS, 2005 April 4 (Box 62)
    - Levante: Theater for Social Change; Levante: Teatro Para Cambio Social (Bilingual, English, Spanish) 46:25, VHS, 2005 April 4 (Box 62)
    - Levante Theater for Social Change;: Teatro Para Cambio Social (Bilingual, English, Spanish) 46:25, mini-DV, 2005 (Box 62)
      Use Copies: DVD use copy available.
    - SAF01: Rehearsal - warm ups, run-through, self intros for performance, mini-DV June 2004 (Box 62)
    - SAF02: Group Interview #1 (in auditorium), outside warm-ups, run-through in auditorium, mini-DV June 2004 (Box 62)
    - SAF03: Run-through (outside), Group Interview #2 (in library), mini-DV June 2004 (Box 62)
    - SAF04: Group Interview #2 continued, photos from booklet upon which characters are based, room tone, mini-DV June 2004 (Box 62)
    - SAF05: Interview with Omar Lainez, en route to performance site, setting up, warming up, mini-DV June 2004 (Box 62)
    - SAF06: Performance - entire play on tripod from one location; interviews with 4 farmworkers, mini-DV June 2004 (Box 62)
    - SAF07: En route to performance site, setting up, warming up, mini-DV June 2004 (Box 62)
    - SAF08: Performance - hand held, from many different places, shots of audience; interviews with 3 farmworkers: #1 is in-camera mic; #2 and #4 are have lav mic; #3 was not taped by this camera, mini-DV June 2004 (Box 62)
    - SAF09: Guitar music (and Legal Aid front door), mini-DV June 2004 (Box 62)
    - SAF10: Interview with Laxmi Haynes, SAF signs, red smilies, mini-DV June 2004 (Box 62)
    - Gigantes en los Campos,interview with Omar Laines, performance #1 at un campo, DAT June 2004 (Box 62)
      Use Copies: CD use copy available.
    - Gigantes Original 2003, Hi8 2003 (Box 62)
    - Untitled, Hi8 undated (Box 62)
    - ¿Que Saco de la Escuela?, Hi8 undated (Box 62)
    - ¿Que Saco de la Escuela?, Gardner - Webb University, VHS-C June 2000 (Box 62)
    - ¿Que Saco de la Escuela?, Nash County Festival Latino, VHS-C July 2000 (Box 62)
    - Farm Worker Awareness Week, Duke, VHS-C March 2001 (Box 62)
    - Los Vendidos @ 2001 AIM Conference, VHS-C March 2001 (Box 62)
    - Los Vendidos, 2nd Nash County performance, VHS-C 2001 (Box 62)
    - Los Vendidos performed @ labor camps in Nash County, VHS-C 2001 (Box 62)
    - ITF audio tapes, 1990-2004, (3 containers) (Box 65)
    - ITF audio tapes, 2004-2005 and undated, (3 containers) (Box 66)
    - ITF documentary discs, 2000-2004 and undated (Box 67)
    - ITF administrative and miscellaneous project discs, 1997-2003 and undated (Box 67)
    - ITF Nuestras Historias mini discs, 2006-2008 (Box 67)
    - ITF documentary CDs, 2000-2004 and undated (Box 68)